A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Vice Presidential, Series 6 FA459
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Vice Presidential, 6
  - Contact Sheets, 1973-1977; 1
    - G2348 - Salute to the President dinner, Chicago, Illinois; Argentine Foreign Minister Guzzetti and Ambassador Musich, 1976 October 7; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 31, Volume 16)
    - G2349 - Salute to the President dinner, Chicago, Illinois, 1976 October 7; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 31, Volume 16)
    - G2350 - Air Force Two crew, 1976 October 7; Color (Box 8, Folder 31, Volume 16)
    - G2351 - Drop-by at Americana Hotel, New York City - Speech to Ukrainians delegation, 1976 October 9; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 32, Volume 16)
    - G2352 - G2354 - Columbus Day reception, New York City, 1976 October 9; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 32, Volume 16)
    - G2355 - Capitol watercolor, copy, 1976 October 13; Color (Box 8, Folder 32, Volume 16)
    - G2356 - G2358 - Salute to the President dinner, New York City, 1976 October 12; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 32, Volume 16)
    - G2359 - G2361 - San Francisco, California, 1976 October 13; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 32, Volume 16)
    - G2362 - G2365 - Portland, Oregon, 1976 October 13; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 32, Volume 16)
    - G2366 - G2370 - Seattle and Everett, Washington, 1976 October 14; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 32, Volume 16)
    - G2371 - Salute to the President dinner, New York City, 1976 October 12; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 32, Volume 16)
    - G2372 - G2381 - Kalamazoo, Saginaw, Grand Rapids and Detroit, Michigan, 1976 October 18; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 32, Volume 16)
    - G2382 - G2388 - Minneapolis and St. Paul, Minnesota, 1976 October 19; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 32, Volume 16)
    - G2389 - Air Force Two crew and staff, 1976 October 19; Color (Box 8, Folder 32, Volume 16)
    - G2390 - Richard Kleindeinst; Venezuelan Ambassador Burelli; Newark, New Jersey, 1976 October 14; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 32, Volume 16)
    - G2391 - Joan Braden (State Department) group; White House Fellows; Linwood Holton and Cynthia Newman, 1976 October 20; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 32, Volume 16)
    - G2392 - Joan Braden (State Department) group; White House Fellows, 1976 October 20; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 32, Volume 32)
    - G2393 - Ambassador Hinton; Donna Blume; President Tubman (Liberia); Association for Children with Learning Disabilities, Wilmington, Delaware, 1976 October 21; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 32, Volume 16)
    - G2394 - G2395 - Reception for Sen. Roth (DE), DuPont residence, 1976 October 21; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 32, Volume 16)
    - G2396 - Association for Children with Learning Disabilities; signing Senate payroll, 1976 October 21; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 32, Volume 16)
    - G2397 - G2399 - National Press Club, 1976 October 26; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 32, Volume 16)
    - G2400 - G2409 - Nassau County, New York, 1976 October 27; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 33, Volume 17)
    - G2410 - Domestic Council staff meeting; Bill Fine; staff meeting, 1976 October 28; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 33, Volume 17)
    - G2411 - Domestic Council staff meeting; staff meeting, 1976 October 28; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 33, Volume 17)
    - G2412 - G2413 - Election eve dinner party, New York City, 1976 November 2; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 33, Volume 17)
    - G2414 - Blume and father; Robert De La Madrid; Cabinet meeting, 1976 November 5; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 33, Volume 17)
    - G2415 - Cabinet meeting, 1976 November 5; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 33, Volume 17)
    - G2419 - Linda Farmer; Donna Blume; Lynn Schenk; Ten Outstanding Women of America; Jon Howe; Women's Advisory Group on Defense, 1976 November 16; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 33, Volume 17)
    - G2420 - Leo A. I. Chance, deputy minister president of the Netherlands Antilles, Sen. Claude Wathey and Ambassador Taummenons Bakker, 1976 November 16; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 33, Volume 17)
    - G2421 - Donna Blume; Ten Outstanding Women of America; Women's Advisory Group on Defense; Leo A. I. Chance, deputy minister president of the Netherlands Antilles; Walter Kiep, West German Minister of Finance, 1976 November 16; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 33, Volume 17)
    - G2422 - Productivity Center symposium; Herman Kahn; Herbert Holloman; Republican Eagles reception, 1976 November 16; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 33, Volume 17)
    - G2423 - Howard Dixon and Donna Blume; Productivity Center symposium; Herman Kahn; Herbert Holloman; Republican Eagles reception, 1976 November 16; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 33, Volume 17)
    - G2424 - G2426 - GRF with Vice President's staff, 1976 November 17; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 33, Volume 17)
    - G2427 - Nancy Hanks; NSC staff, 1976 November 18; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 33, Volume 17)
    - G2428 - G2429 - NSC staff, 1976 November 18; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 33, Volume 17)
    - G2430 - Dr. Norman Hurd; Donna Blume; Henry Catto; swearing-in of Thaddeus Garrett, 1976 November 18; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 33, Volume 17)
    - G2431 - Scowcroft; swearing in of Thaddeus Garrett, 1976 November 18; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 33, Volume 17)
    - G2432 - Jane Orr; Edward Teller; Nancy Hanks, 1976 November 18; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 33, Volume 17)
    - G2433 - G2435 - 22nd annual session of the North Atlantic Assembly, 1976 November 18; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 33, Volume 17)
    - G2437 - G2443 - GRF and Mrs. Ford at Pocantico Hills, 1976 November 20; Color (Box 9, Folder 33, Volume 17)
    - G2444 - G2445 - Dick Starnes; Scripps-Howard; Mary Louise Smith; George Hinman, 1976 November 22; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 33, Volume 17)
    - G2446 - Zarb, Lynn, Cannon, Schmultz; VP-Elect Mondale, 1976 November 24; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 33, Volume 17)
    - G2447 - Dick West, UPI; Jim Deakin, St. Louis Post Dispatch"; Dick Rosenbaum; VP-Elect Mondale ", 1976 November 24; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 33, Volume 17)
    - G2448 - G2457 - Hunting trip to Texas with sons, 1976 November 25; Color (Box 9, Folder 33, Volume 17)
    - G2458 - G2460 - China Institute of America reception, New York, 1976 November 30; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 34, Volume 17)
    - G2461 - Tom Williams promotion ceremony, 1976 December 1; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 34, Volume 17)
    - G2462 - Tom Williams promotion ceremony; George Saunders; Dick West, UPI; Tom Corcoran, 1976 December 1; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 34, Volume 17)
    - G2463 - Pakistan centenary anniversary, 1976 December 1; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 34, Volume 17)
    - G2464 - James Wiehart, New York Daily News;" Pakistan centenary anniversary ", 1976 December 1; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 34, Volume 17)
    - G2465 - George Meany and Bob Armao, 1976 December 3; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 34, Volume 17)
    - G2466 - Donna Blume; John McClenahan; Industry Week"; George Meany and Bob Armao ", 1976 December 3; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 34, Volume 17)
    - G2467 - Craig Berkman; Ambassador Togo, Japan; Walter Oakes; Trudy Feldman, 1976 December 3; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 34, Volume 17)
    - G2468 - G2469 - Luncheon and reception for Italian Prime Minister Andreotti, Italian Embassy, 1976 December 7; Color (Box 9, Folder 34, Volume 17)
    - G2470 - Prime Minister Andreotti at the Washington Monument; Presidential Management Awards, 1976 December 8; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 34, Volume 17)
    - G2471 - Prime Minister Andreotti at Blair House; Prime Minister Andreotti at the Washington Monument; Presidential Management Awards, 1976 December 8; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 34, Volume 17)
    - G2472 - G2473 - Georgetown University graduate student forum, 1976 December 8; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 34, Volume 17)
    - G2473a - James Baker, 1976 December 13; Black and White (Volume 17)
    - G2474 - Shirley Brown; reception for Sen. Scott (PA), British Embassy, 1976 December 13; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 34, Volume 17)
    - G2475 - Joan Braden; Mount Vernon College Political Science Association, 1976 December 14; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 34, Volume 17)
    - G2476 - Mount Vernon College Political Science Association, 1976 December 14; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 34, Volume 17)
    - G2477 - Dr. Constantine, 1976 December 15; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 34, Folder 17)
    - G2478 - John S. Lang; Dr. Constantine, 1976 December 15; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 34, Volume 17)
    - G2480 - Dinner for VP-Elect Mondale, 1976 December 20; Color (Box 9, Folder 34, Volume 17)
    - G2481 - Secret Service presentation to NAR; Larry Eagleburger, 1976 December 20; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 34, Volume 17)
    - G2482 - William Wells; Hugh Sidney; Ambassador Malikyar, Pakistan, 1976 December 21; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 34, Volume 17)
    - G2483 - Ambassador Malikyar, Pakistan, 1976 December 21; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 34, Volume 17)
    - G2484 - VP staff party, 1976 December 22; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 34, Volume 17)
    - G2485 - Dinner for VP-Elect Mondale, 1976 December 20; Color (Box 9, Folder 34, Volume 17)
    - G2486 - G2487 - Mayor Daley funeral, Chicago, Illinois, 1976 December 23; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 34, Volume 17)
    - G2488 - G2490 - Venezuela trip, 1976 December 27; Color (Box 9, Folder 34, Volume 17)
    - G2491 - Venezuela trip, 1976 December 28; Color (Box 9, Folder 34, Volume 17)
    - G2492 - G2496 - Venezuela trip, 1976 December 29; Color (Box 9, Folder 34, Volume 17)
    - G2497 - G2499 - Venezuela trip, 1976 December 31; Color (Box 9, Folder 34, Volume 17)
    - G2500 - G2502 - Venezuela trip, 1976 December 28; Color (Box 9, Folder 35, Volume 18)
    - G2503 - 4-5 Science and Technology Group, 6-37 Newly Elected Senators, Capitol Hill Office, 1977 January 4; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 35, Volume 18)
    - G2504 - 4-9 Science and Technology Group, 10-22 Newly elected senators, Capitol Hill Office, 1977 January 4; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 35, Volume 18)
    - G2505 - Medal of Freedom Award, East Room White House, 1977 January 10; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 35, Volume 18)
    - G2506 - Dinner Honoring Secretary Kissinger at the French Embassy, 1977 January 6; Color (Box 9, Folder 35, Volume 18)
    - G2507 - Presentation to the Vice President from Ambassador of Afghanistan, 1977 January 11; Color (Box 9, Folder 35, Volume 18)
    - G2508 - 4-5 Painting Presentation From Congressman Bill Cohen Senate 212, 6-9 Bruce Caputo, 11-16 Frances Knight, 1977 January 11; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 35, Volume 18)
    - G2509 - Ted Sorensen, 1977 January 11; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 35, Volume 18)
    - G2510 - Presentation of Federal service awards, 1977 January 12; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 35, Volume 18)
    - G2511 - Mrs. Tuna Kopurulu, Washington correspondent from Turkey; presentation of Federal service awards, 1977 January 12; Black and White (Box 9, Folder 35, Volume 18)
  - Negatives, 2
    Conditions Governing Access
    Negatives are restricted from scholarly access. Negatives may be accessed by RAC staff only.
    - G0100-G1150 (Box 10)
    - G1151-G1280 (Box 11)
    - G1281-G1400 (Box 12)
    - G1401-G1525 (Box 13)
    - G1526-G1645 (Box 14)
    - G1646-G1760 (Box 15)
    - G1761-G1900 (Box 16)
    - G1901-G2060 (Box 17)
    - G2061-G2225 (Box 18)
    - G2226-G2350 (Box 19)
    - G2351-G2475 (Box 20)
    - G2476-G2519 (Box 21)
    - Robert A. (Bob) Wands negatives (Box 22)